[
  {
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for the element gold?",
    "choices": ["Au", "Ag", "Fe", "Cu"],
    "answer": "au",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which force is responsible for the attraction between two masses?",
    "choices": [
      "Electromagnetic force",
      "Gravitational force",
      "Nuclear force",
      "Frictional force"
    ],
    "answer": "gravitationalforce",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main function of the ozone layer in the Earth's atmosphere?",
    "choices": [
      "Absorbing ultraviolet radiation",
      "Producing oxygen",
      "Regulating temperature",
      "Generating rainfall"
    ],
    "answer": "absorbingultravioletradiation",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who developed the theory of relativity?",
    "choices": [
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Galileo Galilei",
      "Stephen Hawking"
    ],
    "answer": "alberteinstein",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the basic unit of heredity in living organisms?",
    "choices": ["Protein", "Gene", "Chromosome", "Enzyme"],
    "answer": "gene",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gas is the most abundant in Earth's atmosphere?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Carbon dioxide", "Hydrogen"],
    "answer": "nitrogen",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the chemical formula for water?",
    "choices": ["H2O", "CO2", "CH4", "O2"],
    "answer": "h2o",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known as the \"Blue Planet\" due to its abundant water?",
    "choices": ["Earth", "Mars", "Venus", "Neptune"],
    "answer": "earth",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process by which plants release water vapor into the atmosphere?",
    "choices": [
      "Condensation",
      "Transpiration",
      "Evaporation",
      "Precipitation"
    ],
    "answer": "transpiration",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scientist is credited with the discovery of penicillin?",
    "choices": [
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Alexander Fleming",
      "Marie Curie",
      "Robert Koch"
    ],
    "answer": "alexanderfleming",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main component of Earth's core?",
    "choices": ["Iron", "Nickel", "Copper", "Aluminum"],
    "answer": "iron",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of electromagnetic waves has the shortest wavelength?",
    "choices": ["Radio waves", "Microwaves", "X-rays", "Gamma rays"],
    "answer": "gammarays",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the unit of measurement for electric current?",
    "choices": ["Volt", "Ampere", "Watt", "Ohm"],
    "answer": "ampere",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gas is responsible for the greenhouse effect on Earth?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Carbon dioxide", "Methane"],
    "answer": "carbondioxide",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the largest organ in the human body?",
    "choices": ["Heart", "Liver", "Skin", "Brain"],
    "answer": "skin",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who proposed the heliocentric model of the solar system?",
    "choices": ["Ptolemy", "Copernicus", "Kepler", "Galileo"],
    "answer": "copernicus",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a renewable energy source?",
    "choices": ["Coal", "Natural gas", "Solar power", "Nuclear power"],
    "answer": "solarpower",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of red blood cells in the human body?",
    "choices": [
      "Carrying oxygen",
      "Fighting infections",
      "Clotting blood",
      "Producing antibodies"
    ],
    "answer": "carryingoxygen",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scientist is known for the theory of natural selection?",
    "choices": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Marie Curie"
    ],
    "answer": "charlesdarwin",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the SI unit of pressure?",
    "choices": ["Pascal", "Newton", "Joule", "Kilogram"],
    "answer": "pascal",
    "topic": "science"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of π (pi) to two decimal places?",
    "choices": ["3.14", "2.71", "1.61", "4.20"],
    "answer": "3.14",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a prime number?",
    "choices": ["1", "6", "11", "4"],
    "answer": "11",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a prime number?",
    "choices": ["1", "6", "11", "4"],
    "answer": "11",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a triangle has angles measuring 45°, 45°, and 90°, what type of triangle is it?",
    "choices": ["Equilateral", "Isosceles", "Scalene", "Right-angled"],
    "answer": "right-angled",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the square root of 144?",
    "choices": ["10", "12", "14", "16"],
    "answer": "12",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solve for x: 2x - 5 = 11",
    "choices": ["3", "8", "5", "-3"],
    "answer": "3",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 units and width 5 units?",
    "choices": [
      "13 square units",
      "20 square units",
      "26 square units",
      "40 square units"
    ],
    "answer": "20squareunits",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which trigonometric function is equal to the ratio of the opposite side to the hypotenuse in a right-angled triangle?",
    "choices": ["Sine", "Cosine", "Tangent", "Cotangent"],
    "answer": "sine",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a = 3 and b = 4, what is the value of a² + b²?",
    "choices": ["5", "7", "9", "25"],
    "answer": "25",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 5! (5 factorial)?",
    "choices": ["20", "60", "120", "720"],
    "answer": "120",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the perimeter of a square is 20 units, what is the length of one side?",
    "choices": ["2 units", "4 units", "5 units", "10 units"],
    "answer": "4units",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the identity element for addition?",
    "choices": ["0", "1", "-1", "10"],
    "answer": "0",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of the angles in a hexagon?",
    "choices": ["90 degrees", "120 degrees", "180 degrees", "360 degrees"],
    "answer": "360degrees",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a right-angled triangle has legs measuring 6 units and 8 units, what is the length of the hypotenuse?",
    "choices": ["10 units", "12 units", "14 units", "15 units"],
    "answer": "10units",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of log₂(8)?",
    "choices": ["2", "3", "4", "8"],
    "answer": "3",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a = 2 and b = 3, what is the value of a³ + b³",
    "choices": ["5", "11", "35", "125"],
    "answer": "125",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the midpoint between the points (2, 4) and (6, 8) in a Cartesian coordinate system?",
    "choices": ["(4, 6)", "(3, 5)", "(8, 12)", "(0, 0)"],
    "answer": "(4,6)",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a circle has a radius of 5 units, what is its circumference? (Use π = 3.14)",
    "choices": ["10.5 units", "15.7 units", "31.4 units", "78.5 units"],
    "answer": "31.4units",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the slope of a line passing through the points (3, 5) and (7, 9)?",
    "choices": ["1", "2", "4", "6"],
    "answer": "1",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a square has an area of 36 square units, what is the length of each side?",
    "choices": ["4 units", "6 units", "9 units", "12 units"],
    "answer": "6units",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of sin(30 degrees)? (Use π = 3.14)",
    "choices": ["0.5", "0.75", "1.0", "1.5"],
    "answer": "0.5",
    "topic": "math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which programming language is commonly used for developing mobile applications?",
    "choices": ["Java", "C++", "Python", "Swift"],
    "answer": "swift",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the acronym \"URL\" stand for in the context of web technology?",
    "choices": [
      "Universal Resource Locator",
      "Unified Rendering Language",
      "ser Registration Link",
      "Underlying Resource List"
    ],
    "answer": "universalresourcelocator",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of storage device uses NAND flash memory technology?",
    "choices": [
      "Hard disk drive (HDD)",
      "Solid State Drive (SSD)",
      "CD-ROM",
      "Floppy disk"
    ],
    "answer": "solidstatedrive(ssd)",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a firewall in computer networks?",
    "choices": [
      "To prevent hardware malfunctions",
      "To block unauthorized access",
      "To enhance internet speed",
      "To facilitate data encryption"
    ],
    "answer": "toblockunauthorizedaccess",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which protocol is commonly used for secure communication over the internet?",
    "choices": ["HTTP", "FTP", "HTTPS", "SMTP"],
    "answer": "https",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the context of databases, what does SQL stand for?",
    "choices": [
      "Structured Language",
      "Sequential Query Language",
      "Standard Question Language",
      "Structured Query Language"
    ],
    "answer": "structuredquerylanguage",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a QR code?",
    "choices": [
      "Encoding audio files",
      "Storing contact information",
      "Generating barcodese",
      "Connecting to Wi-Fi networks"
    ],
    "answer": "storingcontactinformation",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which programming paradigm emphasizes the use of functions and procedures?",
    "choices": [
      "Object-oriented programming (OOP)",
      "Procedural programming",
      "Functional programming",
      "Event-driven programming"
    ],
    "answer": "functionalprogramming",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a software application that assists in managing email communication?",
    "choices": ["Spreadsheet", "Database", "Word processor", "Email client"],
    "answer": "emailclient",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which technology is commonly used for wireless communication between devices in close proximity?",
    "choices": ["Bluetooth", "NFC (Near Field Communication)", "Wi-Fi", "GPS"],
    "answer": "bluetooth",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the acronym \"AI\" stand for in the context of technology?",
    "choices": [
      "Advanced Interface",
      "Artificial Intelligence",
      "Automated Integration",
      "Augmented Information"
    ],
    "answer": "artificialintelligence",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which cloud computing service provides virtualized computing resources over the internet?",
    "choices": [
      "Amazon Web Services (AWS)",
      "Microsoft Office 365",
      "Dropbox",
      "Adobe Creative Cloud"
    ],
    "answer": "amazonwebservices(aws)",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a version control system in software development?",
    "choices": [
      "Managing project budgets",
      "Tracking changes in code",
      "Optimizing website performance",
      "Conducting user testing"
    ],
    "answer": "trackingchangesincode",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which programming language is often used for data analysis and machine learning?",
    "choices": ["Java", "R", "Ruby", "PHP"],
    "answer": "r",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a program that replicates itself and spreads to other computers or networks?",
    "choices": ["Spyware", "Malware", "Virus", "Firewall"],
    "answer": "virus",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a type of renewable energy technology?",
    "choices": ["Nuclear power", "Fossil fuels", "Solar power", "Natural gas"],
    "answer": "solarpower",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a VPN (Virtual Private Network)?",
    "choices": [
      "Enhancing internet speed",
      "Securing network connections",
      "Managing databases",
      "Creating virtual machines"
    ],
    "answer": "securingnetworkconnections",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is webvium?",
    "choices": ["Browser", "CSS Framework", "Library", "Social Media"],
    "answer": "browser",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created this chatbot?",
    "choices": ["Mj", "Bill", "Mark", "Jeff"],
    "answer": "mj",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "When did chatbot launch?",
    "choices": ["Nov 2022", "Jun 2023", "Jan 2024", "March 2022"],
    "answer": "nov2022",
    "topic": "technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of marinating meat?",
    "choices": [
      "Enhancing color",
      "Increasing tenderness",
      "Adding sweetness",
      "Reducing cooking time"
    ],
    "answer": "increasingtenderness",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which herb is commonly used in Italian cuisine and is a key ingredient in pesto sauce?",
    "choices": ["Cilantro", "Basil", "Thyme", "Rosemary"],
    "answer": "basil",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What cooking method involves immersing food in hot liquid, often for an extended period?",
    "choices": ["Grilling", "Sautéing", "Boiling", "Roasting"],
    "answer": "boiling",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in guacamole, a popular Mexican dip?",
    "choices": ["Tomatoes", "Avocado", "Onions", "Cilantro"],
    "answer": "avocado",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of pasta is shaped like small rice grains and is often used in soups?",
    "choices": ["Penne", "Orzo", "Fusilli", "Linguine"],
    "answer": "orzo",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of cream of tartar in baking?",
    "choices": [
      "Leavening agent",
      "Flavor enhancer",
      "Acidic stabilizer",
      "Thickening agent"
    ],
    "answer": "acidicstabilizer",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of rice is commonly used in sushi?",
    "choices": ["Basmati", "Jasmine", "Arborio", "Sushi rice"],
    "answer": "sushirice",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "In baking, what does proofing refer to?",
    "choices": [
      "Testing for doneness",
      "Allowing dough to rise",
      "Applying a glaze",
      "Adding seasoning"
    ],
    "answer": "allowingdoughtorise",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key ingredient in the classic French dish coq au vin?",
    "choices": ["Beef", "Chicken", "Lamb", "Fish"],
    "answer": "chicken",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spice is known as the \"queen of spices\" and is often used in both sweet and savory dishes?",
    "choices": ["Cumin", "Turmeric", "Cardamom", "Cinnamon"],
    "answer": "cinnamon",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in the Middle Eastern dish hummus?",
    "choices": ["Chickpeas", "Lentils", "Black beans", "Kidney beans"],
    "answer": "chickpeas",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of lettuce is commonly used in Caesar salads?",
    "choices": ["Romaine", "Iceberg", "Spinach", "Arugula"],
    "answer": "romaine",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of deglazing a pan in cooking?",
    "choices": [
      "Adding flavor",
      "Preventing burning",
      "Cleaning the pan",
      "Making a sauce"
    ],
    "answer": "makingasauce",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a traditional Japanese seasoning made from fermented soybeans?",
    "choices": ["Hoisin sauce", "Miso", "Ponzu sauce", "Mirin"],
    "answer": "miso",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "In barbecue terminology, what is the \"bark\" on smoked meats?",
    "choices": [
      "A type of wood chip",
      "Charred grill marks",
      "Crust formed during smoking",
      "Barbecue sauce coating"
    ],
    "answer": "crustformedduringsmoking",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in the dish ratatouille?",
    "choices": ["Eggplant", "Zucchini", "Bell peppersg", "All of the above"],
    "answer": "alloftheabove",
    "topic": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary muscle targeted during a bicep curl?",
    "choices": ["Quadriceps", "Hamstrings", "Triceps", "Bicepse"],
    "answer": "biceps",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which exercise primarily works the muscles of the chest?",
    "choices": ["Deadlift", "Bench press", "Leg press", "Plank"],
    "answer": "benchpress",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of stretching before a workout?",
    "choices": [
      "Increase heart rate",
      "Build muscle mass",
      "Improve flexibility",
      "Boost endurance"
    ],
    "answer": "improveflexibility",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "In weightlifting, what does the acronym \"RM\" stand for?",
    "choices": [
      "Repetition Maximum",
      "Resting Mode",
      "Resistance Measurement",
      "Recovery Method"
    ],
    "answer": "repetitionmaximum",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of exercise is known for targeting the core muscles?",
    "choices": ["Squats", "Crunches", "Lunges", "Shoulder press"],
    "answer": "crunches",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main benefit of cardiovascular exercise?",
    "choices": [
      "Increased flexibility",
      "Enhanced muscle strength",
      "Improved heart health",
      "Boosted metabolism"
    ],
    "answer": "improvedhearthealth",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which nutrient is essential for muscle repair and growth after a workout?",
    "choices": ["Carbohydrates", "Protein", "Fat", "Fiber"],
    "answer": "protein",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a cool-down after exercise?",
    "choices": [
      "Prevent muscle soreness",
      "Increase adrenaline levels",
      "Enhance muscle activation",
      "Lower heart rate gradually"
    ],
    "answer": "lowerheartrategradually",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which exercise is effective for targeting the gluteal muscles (buttocks)?",
    "choices": ["Calf raises", "Deadlifts", "Plank", "Hip thrusts"],
    "answer": "hipthrusts",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the recommended duration for moderate-intensity aerobic exercise per week, according to fitness guidelines?",
    "choices": ["30 minutes", "60 minutes", "90 minutes", "120 minutes"],
    "answer": "60minutes",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a compound exercise that targets multiple muscle groups?",
    "choices": ["Bicep curl", "Leg press", "Tricep kickback", "Wrist curl"],
    "answer": "legpress",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a stability ball in a workout routine?",
    "choices": [
      "Increase resistance",
      "Improve balance and core strength",
      "Target specific muscle groups",
      "Enhance cardiovascular endurance"
    ],
    "answer": "improvebalanceandcorestrength",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of exercise is known for improving joint flexibility and range of motion?",
    "choices": ["Isometric", "Plyometric", "Flexibility", "Isotonic"],
    "answer": "flexibility",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary energy source for short bursts of high-intensity exercise, such as sprinting?",
    "choices": ["Fats", "Proteins", "Carbohydrates", "Glycogen"],
    "answer": "carbohydrates",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which exercise targets the muscles of the back and is performed by pulling weight toward the chest?",
    "choices": ["Bench press", "Lat pulldown", "Shoulder press", "Leg curl"],
    "answer": "latpulldown",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of interval training in a workout routine?",
    "choices": [
      "Build muscle mass",
      "Increase endurance",
      "Enhance flexibility",
      "Improve balance"
    ],
    "answer": "increaseendurance",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of exercise is characterized by a slow and controlled movement through a full range of motion?",
    "choices": ["Plyometric", "Isometric", "Isotonic", "Dynamice"],
    "answer": "isotonic",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which muscle group does the plank exercise primarily target?",
    "choices": ["Abdominals", "Quadriceps", "Biceps", "Deltoids"],
    "answer": "abdominals",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the recommended rest interval between sets for muscle hypertrophy (muscle growth)?",
    "choices": ["10 seconds", "30 seconds", "1 minute", "3 minutes"],
    "answer": "1minute",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which exercise involves lifting a weight from shoulder height to overhead in one continuous motion?",
    "choices": ["Deadlift", "Clean and jerk", "Snatch", "Military press"],
    "answer": "cleanandjerk",
    "topic": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the horizontal lines on a musical staff?",
    "choices": ["Clefs", "Measures", "Staves", "Ledger lines"],
    "answer": "staves",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which woodwind instrument is known for its double reed and distinctive sound?",
    "choices": ["Clarinet", "Flute", "Oboe", "Saxophone"],
    "answer": "oboe",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "In music notation, what does \"piano\" indicate?",
    "choices": [
      "Play softly",
      "Play loudly",
      "Play with a fast tempo",
      "Play with a slow tempo"
    ],
    "answer": "playsoftly",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is often referred to as the \"King of Pop\"?",
    "choices": ["Michael Jackson", "Elvis Presley", "Prince", "Madonna"],
    "answer": "michaeljackson",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a percussion instrument?",
    "choices": ["Violin", "Trumpet", "Drum", "Piano"],
    "answer": "drum",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which musical genre is characterized by a fast tempo, syncopated rhythms, and improvisation?",
    "choices": ["Jazz", "Classical", "Country", "Blues"],
    "answer": "jazz",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who composed the famous Symphony No. 9, commonly known as the \"Choral Symphony\"?",
    "choices": [
      "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart",
      "Ludwig van Beethoven",
      "Johann Sebastian Bach",
      "Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky"
    ],
    "answer": "ludwigvanbeethoven",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a musical composition for nine instruments or voices?",
    "choices": ["Solo", "Duet", "Trio", "Nonet"],
    "answer": "nonet",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which instrument family does the trumpet belong to?",
    "choices": ["String", "Brass", "Woodwind", "Percussion"],
    "answer": "brass",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"fortissimo\" indicate in sheet music?",
    "choices": [
      "Play softly",
      "Play moderately",
      "Play very loudly",
      "Play with a gradual increase in volume"
    ],
    "answer": "playveryloudly",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which legendary guitarist is known for his work with the band Queen?",
    "choices": ["Eric Clapton", "Jimmy Page", "Brian May", "Jimi Hendrix"],
    "answer": "brianmay",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the standard tuning for a classical guitar's six strings from lowest to highest pitch?",
    "choices": ["E-A-D-G-B-En", "A-D-G-C-E-A", "G-B-E-A-D-G", "D-G-C-F-A-D"],
    "answer": "e-a-d-g-b-e",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "In musical terms, what does \"allegro\" mean?",
    "choices": ["Slow", "Fast", "Loud", "Soft"],
    "answer": "fast",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is often referred to as the \"Queen of Soul\"?",
    "choices": ["Whitney Houston", "Aretha Franklin", "Beyoncé", "Diana Ross"],
    "answer": "arethafranklin",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a traditional Japanese stringed instrument?",
    "choices": ["Banjo", "Sitar", "Shamisen", "Mandolin"],
    "answer": "shamisen",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which musical term indicates a gradual increase in loudness?",
    "choices": ["Crescendo", "Decrescendo", "Staccato", "Legato"],
    "answer": "crescendo",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for his contributions to electronic music and iconic albums like \"Random Access Memories\"?",
    "choices": ["Aphex Twin", "Daft Punk", "Kraftwerk", "Tiesto"],
    "answer": "daftpunk",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a traditional Irish wind instrument with a distinctive sound?",
    "choices": ["Bagpipes", "Flute", "Fiddle", "Tin Whistle"],
    "answer": "tinwhistle",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous composer is known for his \"Moonlight Sonata\" and \"Fur Elise\"?",
    "choices": [
      "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart",
      "Ludwig van Beethoven",
      "Franz Schubert",
      "Johann Sebastian Bach"
    ],
    "answer": "ludwigvanbeethoven",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the standard number of keys on a grand piano?",
    "choices": ["61", "76", "88", "100"],
    "answer": "88",
    "topic": "music"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which sport would you perform a slam dunk?",
    "choices": ["Soccer", "Basketball", "Tennis", "Golf"],
    "answer": "basketball",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 2018?",
    "choices": ["Germany", "Brazil", "France", "Argentina"],
    "answer": "france",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the scoring term for three strikes in a row in bowling?",
    "choices": ["Triple", "Strikeout", "Hat-trick", "Turkey"],
    "answer": "turkey",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "In American football, how many points is a touchdown worth?",
    "choices": ["3", "6", "7", "2"],
    "answer": "6",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Grand Slam tennis tournament is played on clay courts?",
    "choices": ["Wimbledon", "Australian Open", "US Open", "French Open"],
    "answer": "frenchopen",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "In golf, what is the term for completing a hole in one stroke under par?",
    "choices": ["Birdie", "Eagle", "Albatross", "Bogey"],
    "answer": "birdie",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Olympic event includes a combination of skiing, shooting, and cross-country running?",
    "choices": ["Biathlon", "Triathlon", "Pentathlon", "Decathlon"],
    "answer": "biathlon",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the most Olympic gold medals in swimming?",
    "choices": ["Michael Phelps", "Ian Thorpe", "Mark Spitz", "Ryan Lochte"],
    "answer": "Michael Phelps",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sport is known as the \"Sport of Kings\"?",
    "choices": ["Polo", "Horse racing", "Fencing", "Archery"],
    "answer": "horseracing",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a perfect score of 10 in gymnastics?",
    "choices": ["Ace", "Perfect 10", "Bullseye", "Gold standard"],
    "answer": "perfect10",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team won the Super Bowl in 2021?",
    "choices": [
      "New England Patriots",
      "Kansas City Chiefs",
      "San Francisco 49ers",
      "Tampa Bay Buccaneers"
    ],
    "answer": "tampabaybuccaneers",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "In cricket, what is the term for a batsman being declared out without scoring any runs?",
    "choices": ["Duck", "Goose", "Grouse", "Eagle"],
    "answer": "duck",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which athlete is often referred to as \"The Fastest Man on Earth\"?",
    "choices": ["Usain Bolt", "Carl Lewis", "Jesse Owens", "Michael Johnson"],
    "answer": "usainbolt",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a perfect game in bowling (12 consecutive strikes)?",
    "choices": ["Grand Slam", "Perfect 300", "Turkey", "Strikeout"],
    "answer": "perfect300",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which sport can you find a penalty box?",
    "choices": ["Soccer", "Ice hockey", "Cricket", "Baseball"],
    "answer": "icehockey",
    "topic": "sports"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the head of state in the United States?",
    "choices": ["President", "Prime Ministery", "Chancellor", "Monarch"],
    "answer": "president",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a government ruled by a single person with absolute power?",
    "choices": ["Oligarchy", "Monarchy", "Autocracy", "Democracy"],
    "answer": "autocracy",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which branch of government interprets laws and ensures they align with the constitution?",
    "choices": ["Executive", "Legislative", "Judicial", "Administrative"],
    "answer": "judicial",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the United Kingdom, what is the upper house of Parliament called?",
    "choices": [
      "House of Commons",
      "House of Lords",
      "House of Representatives",
      "Senate"
    ],
    "answer": "houseoflords",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary function of the United Nations (UN)?",
    "choices": [
      "International trade regulation",
      "Humanitarian aid",
      "Environmental protection",
      "Global peace and security"
    ],
    "answer": "globalpeaceandsecurity",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the leader of the political party that wins the most seats in the British general election?",
    "choices": [
      "Prime Minister",
      "Chancellor",
      "Speaker of the House",
      "Opposition Leader"
    ],
    "answer": "primeminister",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which document outlines the fundamental principles and laws of a nation?",
    "choices": [
      "Constitutionr",
      "Declaration of Independence",
      "Magna Cartase",
      "Bill of Rights"
    ],
    "answer": "constitution",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the U.S. government, what is the role of the Vice President?",
    "choices": [
      "Head of state",
      "Chief Justice",
      "Presiding officer of the Senate",
      "Speaker of the Houses"
    ],
    "answer": "presidingofficerofthesenate",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country has a system of government known as a federal parliamentary democracy?",
    "choices": ["Germany", "Canada", "China", "Russia"],
    "answer": "canada",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for a political system in which citizens directly vote on laws and policies?",
    "choices": [
      "Representative democracy",
      "Oligarchy",
      "Direct democracy",
      "Totalitarianism"
    ],
    "answer": "directdemocrac",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the current Secretary-General of the United Nations (as of my knowledge cutoff in January 2022)?",
    "choices": [
      "Angela Merkel",
      "Antonio Guterres",
      "Justin Trudeau",
      "Emmanuel Macron"
    ],
    "answer": "antonioguterres",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the official residence of the President of the United States?",
    "choices": [
      "Buckingham Palace",
      "10 Downing Street",
      "The White House",
      "Elysee Palace"
    ],
    "answer": "thewhitehouse",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a form of proportional representation in voting systems?",
    "choices": [
      "First-past-the-post",
      "Single transferable votet",
      "Plurality votingu",
      "Two-round systeme"
    ],
    "answer": "singletransferablevote",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has the power to veto legislation in the United States?",
    "choices": [
      "Speaker of the House",
      "President",
      "Chief Justice",
      "Senate Majority Leader"
    ],
    "answer": "president",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country does the Chancellor serve as the head of government?",
    "choices": ["France", "Germany", "United Kingdom", "Italy"],
    "answer": "germany",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which political ideology emphasizes social equality and collective ownership of resources?",
    "choices": ["Capitalism", "Liberalism", "Socialism", "Conservatism"],
    "answer": "socialism",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the chief executive officer of a U.S. state government?",
    "choices": ["Governor", "Mayor", "Senator", "President"],
    "answer": "governor",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a filibuster in the U.S. Senate?",
    "choices": [
      "To block legislation",
      "To propose new laws",
      "To confirm judicial appointments",
      "To override a veto"
    ],
    "answer": "toblocklegislation",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which political term refers to a sudden and illegal seizure of power from a government?",
    "choices": ["Revolution", "Rebellion", "Coup d'état", "Uprising"],
    "answer": "coupd'état",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the agreement that sets rules for international trade and economic cooperation?",
    "choices": [
      "NATO",
      "Kyoto Protocol",
      "Paris Agreement",
      "World Trade Organization (WTO)"
    ],
    "answer": "worldtradeorganization(wto)",
    "topic": "politics"
  },
  {
    "question": "The capital of _______ is known for its historic landmarks, including the Colosseum and the Vatican City.",
    "answer": "italy",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Photosynthesis is the process by which plants convert sunlight into energy, producing oxygen as a byproduct in the process of _______.",
    "answer": "carbondioxideabsorption",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The law of supply and demand is a fundamental principle in _______ that explains the interaction between producers and consumers in a market.",
    "answer": "economics",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ is the largest planet in our solar system and is known for its prominent Great Red Spot.",
    "answer": "jupiter",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The novel \"To Kill a Mockingbird\" by Harper Lee addresses issues of racial injustice and moral growth in the fictional town of _______.",
    "answer": "maycomb",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The theory of relativity, formulated by _______ in the early 20th century, revolutionized our understanding of space, time, and gravity.",
    "answer": "alberteistein",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Great Barrier Reef, the world's largest coral reef system, is located off the coast of _______.",
    "answer": "australia",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mona Lisa, painted by _______ during the Renaissance, is one of the most famous and iconic artworks in the world.",
    "answer": "leonardodavinci",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The human skeletal system is composed of 206 bones, providing structure and support for the body's various functions, such as _______.",
    "answer": "movementandprotectionoforgans",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The concept of \"survival of the fittest\" is closely associated with _______'s theory of natural selection.",
    "answer": "charlesdarwin",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Eiffel Tower, an iconic landmark, stands in the heart of _______ and attracts millions of visitors each year.",
    "answer": "paris",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ is the largest mammal on Earth and is known for its enormous size and distinctive spout.",
    "answer": "thebluewhale",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The process of converting water into vapor through heating is known as _______.",
    "answer": "evaporation",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The \"Mona Lisa\" is displayed in the _______ Museum, one of the world's most renowned art museums.",
    "answer": "louvre",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The musical genre _______ originated in the African American communities of New Orleans and has diverse styles such as Dixieland and swing.",
    "answer": "jazz",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The neurotransmitter dopamine plays a crucial role in regulating mood, pleasure, and motivation in the _______ system.",
    "answer": "nervous",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ is the process by which plants release water vapor into the atmosphere through small pores in their leaves.",
    "answer": "transpiration",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Taj Mahal, an iconic marble mausoleum, was built in the 17th century in the city of _______.",
    "answer": "agra",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ is a programming language commonly used for web development and is known for its versatility and ease of learning.",
    "answer": "javascript",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The concept of \"supply and demand\" is a fundamental principle in _______ that explains the interaction between producers and consumers in a market.",
    "answer": "economics",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of my creator?",
    "answer": "melvinjonesrepol",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is my name?",
    "answer": "mj",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "TNAAH\n(Hint: A place of worship)",
    "answer": "athan",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "GLEOY\n(Hint: Honor and praise)",
    "answer": "glory",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "NICEAM\n(Hint: A place to watch movies)",
    "answer": "cinema",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "IHSP\n(Hint: A large boat)",
    "answer": "ship",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "EVITAR\n(Hint: Energetic and engaged)",
    "answer": "active",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "ELPORBME\n(Hint: An issue or challenge)",
    "answer": "problem",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "PIRENC\n(Hint: A royal title)",
    "answer": "prince",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "RYOSMTERY\n(Hint: Something difficult to understand)",
    "answer": "mystery",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "TINERNTE\n(Hint: Worldwide computer network)",
    "answer": "internet",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Amazon River is the longest river in the world.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Honey never spoils. Archaeologists have found pots of honey in ancient Egyptian tombs that are over 3,000 years old and still perfectly edible.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the Moon with the naked eye.",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The currency of Switzerland is the Euro.",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mount Everest, the world's highest peak, is located in the Himalayas.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Atlantic Ocean is the largest ocean on Earth.",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cleopatra lived closer in time to the moon landing than to the construction of the Great Pyramid of Giza.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bananas are berries.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift from France to the United States.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bees can recognize human faces..",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Earth is the only planet in our solar system that rotates clockwise.",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Pacific Ocean is shrinking due to the movement of tectonic plates.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mona Lisa has a twin sister.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The speed of light is faster than the speed of sound.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "A group of flamingos is called a \"flock.\"",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Earth's atmosphere is composed primarily of nitrogen.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alaska is the easternmost state in the United States.",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter has the shortest day of all the planets in our solar system..",
    "answer": "false",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Great Barrier Reef is the world's largest single structure made by living organisms.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The platypus lays eggs.",
    "answer": "true",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ mountain in the world is Mount Everest.",
    "answer": "tallest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In winter, polar bears have a __________ layer of fur to keep them warm.",
    "answer": "thick",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ people attended the concert last night.",
    "answer": "many",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The scientist made a __________ discovery that could revolutionize medicine.",
    "answer": "groundbreaking",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ movie I watched last week was both thrilling and suspenseful.",
    "answer": "exciting",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "She owns a __________ collection of rare stamps.",
    "answer": "valuable",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ mountain range stretches across several countries.",
    "answer": "majestic",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the garden, there is a __________ rose blooming with vibrant colors.",
    "answer": "beautiful",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ building in the city is a marvel of modern architecture.",
    "answer": "tallest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The chef prepared a __________ dish using fresh, organic ingredients.",
    "answer": "delicious",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ car on the market is known for its fuel efficiency.",
    "answer": "greenest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the storm, a __________ rainbow appeared in the sky.",
    "answer": "gorgeous",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The team conducted a __________ experiment to test the hypothesis.",
    "answer": "controlled",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ forest is home to a diverse range of wildlife.",
    "answer": "dense",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "My grandmother has a __________ collection of antique furniture.",
    "answer": "priceless",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ apple in the basket was chosen to make the pie.",
    "answer": "juiciest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ skyscraper in the city provides stunning panoramic views.",
    "answer": "tallest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ book on the shelf is a classic that everyone should read.",
    "answer": "oldest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "We had a __________ time at the amusement park, riding roller coasters and enjoying the attractions.",
    "answer": "fantastic",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The __________ student in the class received a special award for academic excellence.",
    "answer": "brightest",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Naruto Uzumaki dreams of becoming the strongest __________ in his village.",
    "answer": "ninja",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the anime 'One Piece,' Monkey D. Luffy searches for the legendary treasure known as the _________.",
    "answer": "onepiece",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Attack on Titan,' humanity battles giant creatures known as __________.",
    "answer": "titans",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saitama, the protagonist of 'One Punch Man,' defeats enemies with just a single __________.",
    "answer": "punch",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'My Hero Academia' is set in a world where people have superpowers, also known as __________.",
    "answer": "quirks",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood' follows brothers Edward and Alphonse Elric as they search for the Philosopher's __________.",
    "answer": "stone",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Demon Slayer,' Tanjiro Kamado joins the Demon Slayer Corps to avenge his family and cure his sister Nezuko from a demon __________.",
    "answer": "curse",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The protagonist of 'Death Note,' Light Yagami, discovers a supernatural notebook that allows him to kill anyone by writing their name in the __________.",
    "answer": "deathnote",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Dragon Ball Z,' Goku achieves a powerful transformation known as __________ Saiyan.",
    "answer": "super",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Sword Art Online' explores the virtual world of Aincrad, where players find themselves trapped in a __________ MMORPG.",
    "answer": "virtual",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'One Piece,' the main character Luffy aims to become the Pirate __________.",
    "answer": "king",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Cowboy Bebop' follows a group of bounty hunters traveling through space on the spaceship __________.",
    "answer": "bebop",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The magical girl series 'Sailor Moon' features a group of girls protecting the world from evil forces, led by the titular character, __________.",
    "answer": "sailormoon",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Hunter x Hunter,' Gon Freecss aspires to become a Hunter and find his missing __________.",
    "answer": "father",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Yu Yu Hakusho' follows Yusuke Urameshi, who is given a second chance at life after sacrificing himself to save a child from a __________.",
    "answer": "car",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The character Inuyasha seeks the Shikon __________ to become a full demon.",
    "answer": "jewel",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Neon Genesis Evangelion' involves the use of giant __________ to combat mysterious beings called Angels.",
    "answer": "mechs",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Bleach' follows Ichigo Kurosaki, who gains the powers of a Soul Reaper after accidentally obtaining a __________.",
    "answer": "zanpakuto",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood,' Edward Elric loses his arm and leg while attempting to perform forbidden __________.",
    "answer": "alchemy",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Fairy Tail' revolves around a guild of wizards, with Natsu Dragneel being a powerful __________.",
    "answer": "firedragonslayer",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The character Light Yagami uses the __________ Death Note to eliminate criminals in 'Death Note'.",
    "answer": "mysterious",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Tokyo Ghoul,' Kaneki Ken transforms into a half-ghoul after a chance encounter with a __________.",
    "answer": "ghoul",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'My Hero Academia' is set in a world where students attend U.A. High School to become professional __________.",
    "answer": "heroes",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The character Kenshin Himura in 'Rurouni Kenshin' is a former __________ seeking redemption for his past actions.",
    "answer": "hitokiri",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "The anime 'Code Geass' features a protagonist named Lelouch vi __________ who gains the power of Geass.",
    "answer": "britannia",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 'Demon Slayer,' Tanjiro Kamado's sister Nezuko becomes a demon after a __________ attack.",
    "answer": "demon",
    "topic": "random"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the main character in Detective Conan?",
    "choices": ["Shinichi Kudo", "Kaito Kuroba", "Heiji Hattori", "Ran Mouri"],
    "answer": "shinichikudo",
    "topic": "anime"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the criminal organization that shrinks Shinichi Kudo into a child in Detective Conan?",
    "choices": [
      "Black Organization",
      "Red Haibara Group",
      "White Syndicate",
      "Blue Crime Ring"
    ],
    "answer": "blackorganization",
    "topic": "anime"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Shinichi Kudo's childhood friend and romantic interest?",
    "choices": ["Kazuha Toyama", "Sonoko Suzuki", "Ai Haibara", "Ran Mouri"],
    "answer": "ranmouri",
    "topic": "anime"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known as the \"Detective of the West\" in Detective Conan?",
    "choices": ["Heiji Hattori", "Conan Edogawa", "Kogoro Mouri", "Gin"],
    "answer": "heijihattori",
    "topic": "anime"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the alias used by Shinichi Kudo when he takes on the identity of a child detective?",
    "choices": [
      "Conan Edogawa",
      "Kaito Kuroba",
      "Heiji Hattori",
      "Saguru Hakuba"
    ],
    "answer": "conanedogawa",
    "topic": "anime"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does SUV stand for in the automotive world?",
    "choices": [
      "Sport Utility Vehicle",
      "Super Urban Van",
      "Speedy Undercarriage Venture",
      "Standard Undercarriage Vehicle"
    ],
    "answer": "sportutilityvehicle",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which car company produces the Mustang model?",
    "choices": ["Chevrolet", "Ford", "Honda", "Toyota"],
    "answer": "ford",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does ABS stand for in relation to car safety?",
    "choices": [
      "Automatic Braking System",
      "All-wheel Brake System",
      "Anti-lock Braking System",
      "Accelerated Brake Setup"
    ],
    "answer": "anti-lockbrakingsystem",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country is known for the automaker Volkswagen?",
    "choices": ["United States", "Germany", "Japan", "Italy"],
    "answer": "germany",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a catalytic converter in a car?",
    "choices": [
      "Improve fuel efficiency",
      "Enhance horsepower",
      "Reduce emissions",
      "Increase tire lifespan"
    ],
    "answer": "reduceemissions",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"horsepower\" measure in a car engine?",
    "choices": ["Speed", "Fuel efficiency", "Engine power", "Car weight"],
    "answer": "enginepower",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for the luxury SUV model called the Range Rover?",
    "choices": ["Mercedes-Benz", "Land Rover", "Audi", "Lexus"],
    "answer": "landrover",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does EV stand for in the context of cars?",
    "choices": [
      "Electric Vehicle",
      "Efficient Van",
      "Engine Vibration",
      "Eco-friendly Vehicle"
    ],
    "answer": "electricvehicle",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "In car terms, what does the acronym RPM stand for?",
    "choices": [
      "Revolutions Per Minute",
      "Racing Performance Mode",
      "Roadside Parking Mechanism",
      "Rapid Power Movement"
    ],
    "answer": "revolutionsperminute",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gas is commonly used in car air conditioning systems?",
    "choices": ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Helium", "Refrigerant (R134a)"],
    "answer": "refrigerant(r134a)",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 4WD stand for in the automotive world?",
    "choices": [
      "Four-Wheel Drive",
      "Forward Wheel Drive",
      "Front Wheel Disengaged",
      "Four-Wheel Drift"
    ],
    "answer": "four-wheeldrive",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for the iconic 911 model?",
    "choices": ["Porsche", "Ferrari", "Lamborghini", "Aston Martin"],
    "answer": "porsche",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a differential in a car?",
    "choices": [
      "Control fuel injection",
      "Transfer power between wheels",
      "Enhance aerodynamics",
      "Regulate tire pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "transferpowerbetweenwheels",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which automaker produces the Prius, a popular hybrid car model?",
    "choices": ["Ford", "Toyota", "Honda", "Chevrolet"],
    "answer": "toyota",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary function of an alternator in a car?",
    "choices": [
      "Generate electricity",
      "Cool the engine",
      "Control suspension",
      "Measure tire pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "generateelectricity",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"MPG\" stand for in car specifications?",
    "choices": [
      "Miles Per Gallon",
      "Maximum Power Gauge",
      "Motor Performance Grade",
      "Maintenance Policy Guide"
    ],
    "answer": "milespergallon",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which car company produces the popular Civic model?",
    "choices": ["Ford", "Honda", "Toyota", "Chevrolet"],
    "answer": "honda",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does CVT stand for in relation to car transmissions?",
    "choices": [
      "Constant Velocity Transmission",
      "Controlled Vibration Technology",
      "Continuous Variable Transmission",
      "Coordinated Valve Timing"
    ],
    "answer": "continuousvariabletransmission",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which luxury car brand has a logo featuring a silver arrow?",
    "choices": ["BMW", "Mercedes-Benz", "Audi", "Jaguar"],
    "answer": "mercedes-benz",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary function of a car's radiator?",
    "choices": [
      "Brake fluid storage",
      "Engine cooling",
      "Fuel injection control",
      "Airbag deployment"
    ],
    "answer": "enginecooling",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which car feature provides better traction on slippery roads?",
    "choices": [
      "Cruise control",
      "ABS brakes",
      "Traction control",
      "Power windowst"
    ],
    "answer": "tractioncontrol",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a turbocharger in a car engine?",
    "choices": [
      "Increase fuel efficiency",
      "Enhance exhaust sound",
      "Improve horsepower",
      "Regulate tire pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "improvehorsepower",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company produces the Wrangler, a popular off-road SUV model?",
    "choices": ["Ford", "Toyota", "Jeep", "Chevrolet"],
    "answer": "jeep",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of a car's shock absorbers?",
    "choices": [
      "Control steering",
      "Absorb road shocks",
      "Regulate fuel injection",
      "Adjust tire pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "absorbroadshocks",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which car component is responsible for igniting the fuel-air mixture in the engine?",
    "choices": ["Spark plug", "Fuel injector", "Alternator", "Radiator"],
    "answer": "sparkplug",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for the luxury SUV model called the Cayenne?",
    "choices": ["Porsche", "BMW", "Audi", "Mercedes-Benz"],
    "answer": "Porsche",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"AWD\" stand for in the automotive world?",
    "choices": [
      "All-Wheel Drive",
      "Automatic Window Display",
      "Accelerated Wheel Drive",
      "Adaptive Wiper Design"
    ],
    "answer": "all-wheeldrive",
    "topic": "cars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company produces the popular Silverado truck model?",
    "choices": ["Ford", "Toyota", "Chevrolete", "Dodge"],
    "answer": "chevrolet",
    "topic": "cars"
  }
]
